Human Resources Division Records UA119
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Human Resources Division Records
1994 -- 2008
1972 -- 2019
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Human Resources
Department of Personnel
UA119
0.63 Linear Feet 2 boxes
5 Digital Object(s)
458 Megabytes
Arrangement
This collection has one series: Unprocessed accession.
Related Materials
UA058 General Administration records
Biographical / Historical
Department of Personnel: Started in 1966. First director was Viola Saltmarsh, former Director of Placement. Personnel functions prior to this department were under the purview of the Director of Placement and the Placement Office which was looks like a predecessor of Student Services/Career Counseling. The Department of Personnel changed its name to the Department of Human Resources in 1988 (or Human Resources Division per the Annual Report of the President to the Trustees, November 4, 1988)
Scope and Contents
This collection contains material related to Human Resources and its Employee Recognition program, including publications, correspondence, and photographs.
Conditions Governing Access
University records are closed for 20 years from the date of their creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Employment and Human Resources
- Additional accessions, 1972 -- 2019; UA119.001
  - Employee Recognition Programs, training, personnel handbooks, 1972 -- 2013; UA119-001 (Box 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Open for research.
  - Periscope Pictures and Training Guide; Distinction Awards DVDs, 1991 -- 2008; UA119-003 (Box 2)
  - One Tufts Fundraising Pamphlets, 2018; UA119-007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2)
  - One Tufts Fundraising Pamphlets, 2019; UA119-008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2)
  - Distinction Awards Ceremony, 2008-June-03; UA119.000011; 1 Digital Object(s); 457.96 Megabytes
  - Employee Handbook, 2008; UA119.000013; 1 Digital Object(s); 342 Kilobytes
  - Employee Handbook, 2010; UA119.000014; 1 Digital Object(s); 434 Kilobytes
  - Human Resources Review, 2008; UA119.000012; 1 Digital Object(s); 155 Kilobytes
  - Human Resources Review, 2009; UA119.000015; 1 Digital Object(s); 114 Kilobytes